let questions=[ //backend
{ numb : 1,
question:"Which of the following is not a primitive data type in Java?",
answer:"string",
options:[
"float",
"int",
"char",
"string"
]
},
{ numb :2 ,
question:"What is the keyword used to implement multiple inheritance in Java?",
answer:"implements",
options:[
"extends",
"implements",
"interface",
"extengs/implements"
]
},
{ numb :3 ,
question:"In Java, which keyword is used to create a new instance of a class?",
answer:"new",
options:[
"new",
"instance",
"create",
"object"
]
},
{ numb : 4,
question:"What is the default value of a local variable in Java?",
answer:"depends on the data type",
options:[
"0",
"depends on the data type",
"null",
"undefined"
]
},
{ numb : 5,
question:"Which data structure uses a Last-In-First-Out (LIFO) order?",
answer:"Stack",
options:[
"Queue",
"Stack",
"List",
"Map"
]
},
{ numb : 6,
question:"What is the parent class of all Java classes?",
answer:"Object",
options:[
"Object",
"Main",
"Class",
"Super"
]
},
{ numb :7 ,
question:"Which of the following is used to handle exceptions in Java?",
answer:"All of the above",
options:[
"try",
"catch",
"throw",
"All of the above"
]
},
{ numb : 8,
question:"Which collection in Java does not allow duplicate elements?",
answer:"HashSet",
options:[
"Arraylist",
"Linkedlist",
"HashSet",
"HashMap"
]
},
{ numb :9 ,
question:"What is the purpose of the this keyword in Java?",
answer:"To refer to the current instance of the class.",
options:[
"To create a new object.",
"To refer to the current instance of the class.",
"To access superclass methods and properties.",
"To create a new instance of a subclass."
]
},
{ numb : 10,
question:"Which of the following is not a valid declaration of a String in Java?",
answer:"String s = 'H';",
options:[
"String s = Hello;",
"String s = 'H';",
"String s = new String(Hello);",
"String s = ;"
]
},
];